http://sexualastrology.com/privacy_statement.html#cookie-policy

Custom Search
... READ HOW THE STARS AFFECT YOUR SEX LIFE ...
Personalized Horoscopes and Astrology Reports!
Home
Your Privacy:
At SexualAstrology.com, we are committed to respecting your privacy. We
recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about
yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. That's why we have
put a policy in place to protect your personal information. You may always
visit our site and browse without giving us any personal information. Please
read on for more details about our privacy practices.
What information does
SexualAstrology.com collect and how do we use it?
At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal
information. Generally this information is requested when you register for
an online service or when you provide information in connection with an
online transaction.
When you order, we
ask you for your name, e-mail address, shipping and billing addresses,
telephone number, and credit card information.
When you enter a
contest or other promotional event, we may ask for your name, address,
telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and
notify winners.
If you choose to
give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business
partners may need - to correspond with you, process a credit card order,
or deliver a product for example, it is our intent to let you know how
we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to
have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we
will respect your wishes.
SexualAstrology.com,
the service providers for it, and all vendors providing products or
services through our web site use your personal information: to operate
our web site and/or effect your transactions; to create and share
reports about your transactions among themselves; and to perform credit
fraud screening services for transactions between you and us and/or
others.
We intend to
continue improving the content and function of SexualAstrology.com. For
this reason, we monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help
us improve the design and layout of our site and provide content of
interest to you.
Cookie Policy
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser
on your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable Google to provide you with
more personal ad service. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but
you can usually change your browser to prevent that if you would rather not
store the information for future use.
Google AdSense Cookie:
This website uses cookies to personalize ads. (Google AdSense)
For more information on Google AdSense go to Google's Ads Preference Manager available here: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/.
You may opt-out of the Google Adsense partner network cookie at:
https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin.
However, the opt-out option utilizes a cookie. If you clear your browsers cookies you opt-out cookie will be deleted as well and not maintained.
In order to resolve this visit Google browser plug-in at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin
Your consent.
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this
information by SexualAstrology.com. If we decide to change our privacy
practices, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always
kept informed of what data we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances we disclose it. Please check this page for changes from time
to time to make sure you are aware of our latest privacy practices.
Because SexualAstrology.com is globally accessible, we may make information we
gather available to our worldwide business units. For those of you visiting
us from the European Economic Area, please note that the personal data you
enter will be transferred outside the European Economic Area for use by
SexualAstrology.com and its affiliates for any of the purposes described
above. By using our web site and providing us with your personal data, you
consent to this transfer of your personal data.
The privacy of our visitors to SexualAstrology.com is important to us.
At SexualAstrology.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of
personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit SexualAstrology.com, and how we safeguard your information. We
never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your
IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit
our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
We also use third party advertisements on SexualAstrology.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such
as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the
Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some
cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to
someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone
who frequents cooking sites).
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Googleís DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are
browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is
used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (îinterest based targetingî). The ads served will be targeted based on your
previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel
advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses ìnon personally identifiable
informationî. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone
number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites
using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing
preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as
well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or
accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow
cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
AdSense Privacy Policy Provided by JenSense
Will SexualAstrology.com
disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
SexualAstrology.com may store and disclose personal information as allowed
or required by applicable law, including making disclosures that are
necessary or advisable to: (a) protect the rights, safety or property of
users of our web site, the public, or SexualAstrology.com or our web site
suppliers; and (b) conform to legal or regulatory requirements.
Personal data (usually referred to just as "data" below) will only be processed by us to the extent necessary and for the purpose of providing a functional and user-friendly website, including its contents, and the services offered there.
Per Art. 4 No. 1 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679, i.e. the General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter referred to as the "GDPR"), "processing" refers to any operation or set of operations such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation, alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination, or otherwise making available, alignment, or combination, restriction, erasure, or destruction performed on personal data, whether by automated means or not.
The following privacy policy is intended to inform you in particular about the type, scope, purpose, duration, and legal basis for the processing of such data either under our own control or in conjunction with others. We also inform you below about the third-party components we use to optimize our website and improve the user experience which may result in said third parties also processing data they collect and control.
Our privacy policy is structured as follows:
I. Information about us as controllers of your dataII. The rights of users and data subjectsIII. Information about the data processing
I. Information about us as controllers of your data
The party responsible for this website (the "controller") for purposes of data protection law is:
SexualAstrology.comadmin@sexualastrology.com
II. The rights of users and data subjects
With regard to the data processing to be described in more detail below, users and data subjects have the right
to confirmation of whether data concerning them is being processed, information about the data being processed, further information about the nature of the data processing, and copies of the data (cf. also Art. 15 GDPR);
to correct or complete incorrect or incomplete data (cf. also Art. 16 GDPR);
to the immediate deletion of data concerning them (cf. also Art. 17 DSGVO), or, alternatively, if further processing is necessary as stipulated in Art. 17 Para. 3 GDPR, to restrict said processing per Art. 18 GDPR;
to receive copies of the data concerning them and/or provided by them and to have the same transmitted to other providers/controllers (cf. also Art. 20 GDPR);
to file complaints with the supervisory authority if they believe that data concerning them is being processed by the controller in breach of data protection provisions (see also Art. 77 GDPR).
In addition, the controller is obliged to inform all recipients to whom it discloses data of any such corrections, deletions, or restrictions placed on processing the same per Art. 16, 17 Para. 1, 18 GDPR. However, this obligation does not apply if such notification is impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. Nevertheless, users have a right to information about these recipients.
Likewise, under Art. 21 GDPR, users and data subjects have the right to object to the controller's future processing of their data pursuant to Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f) GDPR. In particular, an objection to data processing for the purpose of direct advertising is permissible.
III. Information about the data processing
Your data processed when using our website will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose for its storage ceases to apply, provided the deletion of the same is not in breach of any statutory storage obligations or unless otherwise stipulated below.
Model Data Protection Statement for Anwaltskanzlei Weiﬂ & Partner
Tell us what you think.
Our goal is to respect your privacy. To help us improve our privacy
policies, please give us your
feedback. We welcome your comments and questions.
New Age Reports:New WomanNew ManNew Gay ManNew Lesbian Woman
”
1999 - 2020
Sexual Astrology - sexualastrology.com - All rights reserved.
| Disclaimer | Privacy Statement | Sitemap |
